{
    "id": "039fe7b8c19a46b6b6b6b9f21ad39ff0",
    "title": "Simple future tense",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "db3a249d4a21450eac4767f2f01e9236",
            "title": "Simple Future Tense Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "In two days, I ………………….. my results.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will know",
                        "would know",
                        "will be knowing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘There is the doorbell.’ ‘I ………………..’",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "would go",
                        "am going",
                        "will go"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "You ..................... this decision.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will be regretting",
                        "will regret",
                        "would regret"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We ………………….. what happened to her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "would never know",
                        "will never know",
                        "will never be knowing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The whole nation ……………….. proud of you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "will be",
                        "would be"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "That …………………. our gift to the school.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will be",
                        "would be",
                        "will have been"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Kind words ………………….. others joy.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will give",
                        "would give",
                        "will be giving"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "This piece of wisdom ………………. you ten dollars.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will cost",
                        "would cost",
                        "will be costing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You ..................... my position.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will never understand",
                        "would never understand",
                        "never understand"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Someday I ........................ a novel.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will be writing",
                        "will write",
                        "would write"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ...................... this.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "will not permit",
                        "would not permit",
                        "will not be permitting"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He .....................… the test.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "cannot pass",
                        "will not pass",
                        "will not be passing"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}